Hello Hello
Guys Welcome Back To The Video So
Guys The
Final Year Sure First Quarterly
Results Of Lombard General Insurance Company Are Out So In This Video
We Will See That The Company Has Improved Its Performance In June
And We Will Also Check The Fundamentals Of The Company
And See If This Company Is Worth Money Along With That
We Will Discuss About The Technicals Of The Company
So Let's Start The Video With The Fundamentals Of This Company
Subscribe Channel
I Am Going To Discuss About The Business Of The Company So
It Is One Of The Leading
General Insurance Companies In India This
Company Is A Very Bsc International Student And
If We Discuss About Some Important Figures Of This Company Then
1508 5 Rotiyas
Company's Market Cap Titu Ki Peech Which Is
Very High 19.2 Percent The Company
's Charges Sine 15.1 Percent The Company's Return
On Equity Last Six Months Twitter Has
Gone Negative Bar Almost
12 Per Cent And Last 3 Years' Joe Shells  The
dropped metric is coming out to be around 13%
while it is okay,
tweeting it is much above the book value, this dividend
yield point is around 4%, Edifice is very much ₹10, till now the
June quarter of this company, but if we
discuss about diesel, then guys, the
June 2017 quarterly results are in front of you
and here all the half
values ​​are given in lax,
but don't worry about it,
even after converting every value into course, I will
tell you that in the June 2017 quarter, the
company has
generated an income of 39.78.20 and almost
15.15 profit and this is the
profit after tax of the company and if the same
result is taken from the June 21 quarter, then
in the June 2nd quarter, the company had
posted an income of 38.37 products and
almost no profit, meaning if these
terms of income are seen, then the growth is quite
minimal, but if in terms of  If we
look at the profit, show the company Apple Inc. Bottle Jabardast in
June 2012 quarter computer
June
21 last quarter, that is, if
seen in comparison to 50 quarters, then in March 20
quarter the company
generated an income of 14600 36.34 and Missing
Problem 19.51 Protein Prof that in
terms of income the company has posted less profit
in June 2017 quarter computer
March 21 but in this quarter the company has
posted more profit by controlling its expenses in June 2012
quarter computer March so you
can clearly see that and if you just look at the expenses of this company
here, then
how the company has given more profit by controlling its expenses, that is,
despite having less income in June 2018 quarter, that is, the
June quarter liquidity
turned out to be very tremendous. Let us discuss about the
health of the balance sheet of this company. So
in the June 2012 quarter the company increased its results.
What does it mean that the balance sheet has helped
improve? In the June 2012 quarter and if we
look at it overall, the
existing company has ten times the debt in comparison, which
means it is a very debt-free company
and overall the balance sheet is set, then it is
tremendous. Now look at this company, if I
discuss about the holding pattern with you, then by the June turn, the share
holding pattern has not been decided yet, but
if we look at the March turn, then the
promoters and examinees link it to it,
other jewelers had invested in the March
2018 quarter and if we look at the public, then guys,
if you can see the
holding of a big retailer and if you calculate it, then the
holding of a small retailer like us in this company is coming out to be
around 70 percent as written in the box, so
guys, now it comes down to the condition whether
you people should invest in this company
or not, so look guys, the growth of the company
in the short term, that is, the need for June scam, is
quite tremendous, so you people can
definitely make a short term investment plan
in this company.  But if you want to go for a long-term class, then
I will suggest you that if you have
faith in the company, you can definitely go for it later. It was simply amazing to see this in the short term that
you
can invest in this company differently. The results of the June quarter are coming out to be
quite tremendous. We will
discuss the tax of this company so far. So guys,
here we have come to the invest daily
chart. First of all, let us understand how the company is doing right now.
You
can clearly see that a team
pattern acid double top pattern is forming on the company.
If this pattern breaks out,
then you
can target from 2050 to 1100 rupees from this
company. So, for those who want to do
investment planning for the long term in this chapter, I will advise them to
wait for a few more days. If its
breakout happens towards the downside, then
you will get
entry into this company at a very low price point. And if the
breakout happens towards the downside, then it would be expensive.  So right now
you can trade around the current market price,
which is a strong support
base for this company. As you
can clearly see here, you wo
n't incur much loss in these terms and conditions. And as far as winters are concerned,
look, guys, now let's take
a vote on the companies, to wait
for devotional confirmation from difficulties.
So when this company
shows universal confirmation,
after universal confirmation, you
can plan the buy and take the fastest 1857 Tagore and 14
of ₹100 and from there, the company, this
support of yours, ₹5, company goes
up with this support. So,
after the reversal confirmation, you can log in and plan your trip.
Health Katwa 14 is a very important
level in front of the years.
If you want, you can take a screenshot and
show it to the doctors. You can do that too. So, guys, see you
in the next video. Thanks
for watching. And guys, if you  If you have any
doubt in your mind related to quality stock market or
any stock then you
can ask me by commenting in the comment section or else
I have given you the link of Instagram
in the description box, you
can go and game me immediately Hanuman
Conversation Thanks again for watching raised
by gas and definitely from this stage